A Guide to the Executive Papers of Governor Andrew J. Montague, 1884-1907 (bulk 1902-1905)
Library of Virginia
- Series IV. Personal Papers, 1895-1906 (bulk 1902-1905)., Extent: 24 boxes. (Box 29-53)
  - Subseries B: Subject Files, 1895-1906., 3 boxes.
    - McCue Clemency
      - W, 1905 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Receipts
      - A-G, 1895-1902 (Box 52, Folder 25)
      - H-P, 1899-1902 (Box 52, Folder 26)
      - Q-Y, 1899-1902 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Telegrams
      - A-K, 1902-1905 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - L-Y, 1902-1905 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Oversized, 1899-1906
  - Correspondence (Chronological)
    - 1902 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - 1903 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - 1904 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - 1905-1906 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (Alphabetical)
    - Capitol Enlargement-Thanksgiving Proclamations, 1899-1905 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Quarterly Reports (Newport News Quarantine Stations), 1901-1906 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Personal Papers (Chronological Files), 1903-1906 (Box 55, Folder 3)